for everyone how we can get API and
open I firstly go to this websites
and then after that you can find
your secret API on this link click
here just wait a
second yeah you must have uh and open
a account uh or you should create an
account I have account now I'm Ling
with my account yeah here and after
that inter password then click
continue in here create an API to
access the open AP okay create new
one project like this doesn't matter project
project default project secret K this is
your uh AP ik you can use your project
and use on other project use the AI uh
now uh open a okay you should p in
here and and after that you should save
then you can use on your project this is your API
K thank you for watching my video have a great day